Finding Aid for the William Campbell Binkley Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- 1 roll of microfilm, unidentified (Box 40 (7))
MOFFITT, James W. (Oklahoma Historical Society, Bessie Tift College) - 4 (1936, 1942, 19V+, 1947)
MOGER, Allen W. (Washington and Lee University) - 4 (1943, 194, 1947)
MOLLETf, Carlie (H.E. Huntington Library) - 2 (1937)
MONAGHAN, J. (Illinois State Historical Society) - 2 (1944)
MONROE, Haskell (Texas A 8c M University) - 1 (Sept. 15, 1964)
MONTGOMERY, C. D. - 1 (Feb. 2, 1959)
MONTGOMERY, C. M. (Pi Kappa Alpha Fraternity, University of Texas) - 4 (1921, 1923, 1924)
MONTGOMERY, Horace (University of Georgia) - 1 (Jan. 27, 1950)
MOOD, Fulmer (University of California Library) - 3 (1943, n.d.)
MOODY, L. S. (Chamber of Commerce of Augusta) - 1 (July 30, 1945)
MOOK, Maurice A. (American University) - 2 (1942, 1943)
M00NEY, Chase (University of Mississippi, Brenau College, War Department, Indiana University) - 93 (1938-63) (including 1 each from B.I. Wiley and John L. Snell)
MOORE, A. B. (University of Alabama) - 17 (1931, 1935, 1936, 1942, 1944, 1946, 1947, 1958)
MOORE, Dan Tyler (International Platform Association) - 1 (Nov. 25, 1964)
MOORE, Eoline Wallace (Birmingham-Southern College) - 1 (Mar. 18, 1946)
MOORE, Glover (Mississippi State College) - 17 (1933, 1936, 1937, 1941, 1943, 1948, 1952, 1967)
MOORE, Mary D. (Tennessee Division of Library and Archives) - 1 (May 5, 1942)
MORGAN, W. H. (Morgan, Napier Company) - 1 (Aug. 21, 1936)
MORRIS, Richard B. (Princeton Institute for Advanced Study) - 1 (Feb. 2, 1948)
MORROW, Josephine (Colorado College) - 3 (1922, 1924)
MORROW, Ralph E. (Washington University) - 2 (1957, 1961)
MORTON, D. Walter (Syracuse University) - 1 (Sept. 23, 1935)
MORTON, Richard L. (The William and Mary Quarterly) - 6 (1944-46)
MOWRY, George E. (War Production Board, University of California, Mississippi Valley Historical Association) - 6 (1944, 1951, 1952, n.d.)
MUMFORD, L. Quincey (Librarian of Congress) - 1 (Aug. 1, 1958)
MUNDEN, Ken (Society of American Archivists) - 2 (1964, 1965)
MUNGER, Lilla - 1 (Dec. 22, 1922)
MUNRO, Dana C. - 1 (Mary 29, 1929)
MUNRO, Dana G. - 1 (Oct. 20, 1941)
MURPHY, Gardner (City College of New York) - 1 (July 29, 1943)
MURPHY, Malcolm - 7 (1926, 1928-30)
MURRAY, John W. (Murray Drug Company) - 1 (Sept. 23, 1935)
MUSSED, J. H. (Dental Specialty Company) - 2 (1922)
MYERS, Edward D. (Southern Humanities Conference) - 6 (1950, 1951)
NAPIER, T. H. (Alabama College) - 1 (Aug. 8, 1939)
NASATIER, Abraham - 1 (Dec. 2, 1920)
NAVAL Administrative Office - 1 (Feb. 19, 1957)
NAVY Department, Bureau of Naval Personnel - 3 (1945) (including 1 each from Germain R. Row, F. V. Lawrence, Jr., and Elizabeth G. Grimsley)
NAWTHEY, Arno (University of Texas) - 1 (June 7, 1963)
NAYLOR, Joe A. (The Naylor Company) - 1 (Apr. 4, 1941)
NEILL, Robert T. (Hill, Neill & Hill) - 1 (Nov. 5, 1923)
NELSON, B. H. (Clark College) - 1 (Oct. 29, 1945)
NELSON, Frank A. - 2 (1948)
NELSON, Walter R. - 1 (Sept. 26, 1959)
NETTELS, Curtis P. (University of Wisconsin, American Historical Association) - 12 (1941)
NEU, C. T. (East Texas State Teachers College) - 1 (May 18, 1936)
NEUHAUS, Elizabeth (The History Majors' Committee) - 1 (Mar. 29, 1928)
NEUMANN, Alfred R. (University of Houston) - 2 (1965)
NEW BOLD, Catharine (State University of New ifork, Albany) - 1 (Apr. 9, 1964)
NEVLON, Lulu M. - 6 (1921, 1922, n.d.)
NEWMAN, Andrew J. (University of Kansas) - 1 (Aug. 24, 1920)
NEWSOME, A. R. (North Carolina Historical Commission) - 1 (Mar. 2, 1934)
NICHOLS, Jeannette P. - 8 (1938, 1939, 1945, 1946)
NICHOLS, Roy F. (University of Pennsylvania) - 14 (1934-36)
NICHOLSON, W. B. (Austin Peay Normal School) - 1 (Sept. 30, 1937)
NIEHAUS, E. F. - 1 (July 1956)
NIXON, H. C. (Tulane University) - 2 (1935, 1936)
NIXON, Raymond B. (Emory University) - 2 (1945)
NOBLE, Dorothy - 1 (Jan. 30, 1940)
NOBLIN, Stuart - 1 (Jan. 6, 1946)
NORLIN, President (Secretary) (University of Colorado) - 1 (Aug. 19, 1929)
NORRIS, Joe L. (Wayne State University) - 1 (Apr. 15, 1957)
NORTHWESTERN University History Department - 1 (Mar. 17, 1941)
OAKES, Mildred (Tulane University) - 1 (Dec. 14, 1965)
OAKES, William J. (Memorial Junior High School) - 1 (Feb. 20, 1935)
O'BRIEN, C. Bickford (University of California) - 1 (Feb. 26, 1959)
O'CALLAGHAN, H. N. (First American National Bank) - 2 (1950, 1953)
O'CONNOR, Thomas - 1 (Oct. 17, 1930)
O'DELL, Frances M. (Tennessee Historical Society) - 1 (Oct. 24, 1963)
ODUM, Howard W. (University of North Carolina) - 1 (Nov. 14, 1935)
O'KEEFE, W. F. (Doubleday, Doran & Co.) - 1 (May 1, 1944)
OLDFATHER, C. H. (University of Nebraska) - 1 (May 31, 1932)
OLSON, James C. (Mississippi Valley Historical Review, University of Nebraska) - ll8 (1953-56, 1963, 1966) (including 4 from Patricia French, 2 each from O.M. Dickerson and Jay F. W. Pearson, and 1 each from Eric H. Boehm, Mary Ann Davis, Russell W. Fridley, Sarah B. Holland, R. W. G. Vail, and William G. Wilson)
OSBORN, F. H. (War Department) - 1 (Feb. 9, 1942)
OSBORN, George C. (Memphis State College, University of Florida) - 4 (1943, 1946-48)
OSBORNE, Lithgow (American-Scandinavian Foundation) - 1 (Feb. 24, 1950)
OSBORNE, Louise - 1 (May 21, 1950)
OSBORNE, Mary H. (University of North Carolina) - 1 (Feb. 1, 1950)
OSWALD, Gertrude Casebier (Sherman Junior High School) - 4 (1960, n.d.)
OVERSTREET, J. W. (Winston County Agricultural High School) - 1 (Feb. 11, 1931)
OVERTON, Richard C. (Chicago, Burlington & Quincy Rail Road Company, Northwestern University) - 11 (1945, 1950, 1962)
OWEN, David (American Historical Association, Harvard University) - 7 (1949, 1950)
OWEN, Marie B. (Alabama Department of Archives and History) - 2 (1934, 1937)
OWINGS, Donnell M. (University of Oklahoma) - 1 (Feb. 8, 1950)
OWSLEY, Frank Lawrence (Vanderbilt University, University of Alabama) - 48 (1930-33, 1935, 1937-40, 1942, n.d.) (including 1 each from Fletcher M. Green, Frank Q. Crockett, James A. Barnes, J.H. Parks, and Howard K. Beale)
OWSLEY, Harriet Chappell (Tennessee State Library and Archives) - 20 (1953, 1956-60, 1964) (including 1 each from Roger W. Shugg and Ken Munden)
PAGE, Mary F. - 2 (1948, n.d.)
PAINE, Alice T. (University of North Carolina Press) - 2 (1949)
PAINE, Clara S. (Mississippi Valley Historical Association) - 229 (1923, 1936, 1938-41, 1943-54, 1956, n.d.) (including 1 letter each from Paul M. Angle, Thomas L. Bailey, John D. Barnhart, Thomas D. Clark, Elmer Ellis, Curtis W. Garrison, J. L. Highsaw, Albert L. Kohlmeier, George E. Mowry, and Grace Lee Nute)
PAINE, Clarence S. (Beloit College Libraries, Oklahoma City Libraries) -10 (1946, 1950, 1951, 1953) (including 1 from S. Moinul Haq)
PALMER, Frank C. (University of California) - 1 (Feb. 24, 1925)
PALMER, Stuart (American Education Fellowship) - 1 (July 20, 1945)
PANKEY, Clyde Ely (Laurel School) - 2 (1947)
PAPILLON, Cicely G. - 1 (Feb. 15, 1946)
PARGELLIS, Stanley (Newberry Library) - 11 (1944, 1945, 1948) (including 1 from E. E. Dale)
PARK, Laurine - 3 (1927, 1930) parker, Gordon (Colorado College) - 5 (1926-29, 1935) parker, Marie Hammond - 1 (Feb. 10, 1953)
PARKER, William A. (American Council of Learned Societies) - 1 (Apr. 28, 1950)
PARKS, E. T. (Berea College) - 2 (1943)
PARKS, Edd Winfield - 5 (1936, 1938, 1939, 1944) (University of Georgia)
PARKS, J. H. (Birmingham-Southern College, Florida State College for Women) 2 (1943, 1946)
PARKS, Norman L. - 16 (1929, 1931-33) (including 1 each from Thomas P. Abernethy, Thomas S. Staples, and G.A. O'Neal)
PARMER, J. Norman (Northern Illinois University) - 2 (including 1 from Darla Owen) (1961)
PASCHAL, F. C. (Vanderbilt University) - 10 (1930-33, 1935, 1936) (including 1 each from Jane Sutherland and P. E. Minor)
PATRICK, Rembert W. (University of Florida, Florida Historical Society, Southern Historical Association) - 3 (1956, 1962, 1966)
PATTERSON, C. Perry (University of Texas) - 2 (1921)
PATTERSON, Ernest Minor (American Academy of Political and Social Science) 2 (1910, 1938) (including 1 to F. W. hoore from Rednard Gumplowicz)
PATTERSON, John C. (American University) - 5 (1930, 1940) (including 1 from Charles W. Hackett)
PATTIE, Frank (Rice Institute) - 1 (Aug. 13, 1946)
PATTON, James W. (Converse College, Southern Historical Association, University of North Carolina Library) - 60 (1935, 1941-49, 1951, 1956, 1958) (including 1 from The Franklin Press)
PATY, Sadie - 1 (Aug. 8, 1943)
PAULISSEN, Bob (American Transfer and Storage Co.) - 1 (May 24, 1967)
PAXSON, Frederic L. - 1 (Aug. 28, 1946)
PEARCE, H. J. (Brenau College) - 3 (1939, 1940)
PEASE, F. S., Jr. (Appleton-Century-Crofts) - 25 (1935-36)
PECK1IAM, Howard H. (Indiana Historical Bureau) - 8 (1948, 1949, 1953)
PEDERSON, Lora Lee - 1 (Aug. 20, 1945)
PEELER, Elizabeth (Southwestern College, Birmingham-Southern College) -4 (1941-43)
PEERY, William (Tulane University) - 1 (July 3, 1963)
PEGG, C. H. (University of North Carolina) - 2 (1935)
PEIRCE, Paul S. - 2 (1942, 1943)
PELZER, Louis (State University of Iowa, Mississippi Valley Historical Review) - 37 (1924, 1925, 1930, 1936-39, 1941-46)
PELZER, Mildred W. - 1 (Nov. 8, 1946)
PERKINS, Clarence (University of North Dakota) - 1 (Dec. 4, 1928)
PERKINS, Dexter (American Historical Association) - 1 (Feb. 27, 1931)
PERKINS, Howard C. (Bradley University) - 8 (1942, 1945-47, 1949)
PERKINS, Lindsey S. (Brooklyn College) - 1 (May 28, 1947)
PERRY, Ralph (Tennessee Executive Chamber) - 2 (1936)
PETERSON, William J. (State Historical Society of Iowa, State University of Iowa, Iowa Authors Club) - 22 (1938, 1939, 1942-44, 1946, 1948, 1950-53, n.d.) (including 1 from Thomas E. Martin)
PHELPS, Hilda Wilcox - 1 (May 1, 1944)
PHELPS, Shelton (Peabody College, Winthrop College) - 3 (1933, 1939, 1941)
PHILLIPS, Dayton (Vanderbilt University) - 14 (1949, 1951-53, 1964)
PHILLIPS, Ulrich B. (Yale University) - 6 (1932-33)
PICKENS, A. L. - 1 (July 23, 1946)
PIERCE, Cornelia M. (Carnegie Institution of Washington) - 2 (1932)
PIPHER, Charlotte Applewhite (Tulane University Library) - 1 (Apr. 8, 1946)
PITTMAN, Marvin S. (South Georgia Teachers College, Georgia Teachers College) - 6 (1934, 1935, 1940, 1943)
POMFRET, John E. (College of William and Mary, Vanderbilt University, Social Science Research Council) - 20 (1936-42, 1944-46, 1948, n.d.) (including 1 each from C. M. Sarratt and H. Clay Reed)
PORTER, Livingstone - 1 (July 13, 1920)
POSEY, Walter Brownlow (Birmingham-Southern College, Agnes Scott College, Emory University, Southern Historical Association) - 66 (1930-35, 1937, 1938, 1941-51, 1953, 1956-58) (including 1 each from Phil Williams, William D. McCain, and W.H. Stephenson)
POSTLETHWAITE, W. W. (Colorado College, Winter Night Club) - 4 (1922, 1926, 1927)
POTTER, David M. (Yale University) - 2 (1943, 1949)
POTTER, Kenneth (West Coast Relays) - 1 (Apr. 25, 1932)
PRICE, Grady D. - 1 (Nov. 29, 1943)
PRICE, N. II. (West End High School) - 1 (Feb. 8, 1936)
PRICHARD, Walter (Louisiana State University) - 2 (1937)
PRIEST, J. Percy (U.S. Congress) - 1 (Nov. 9, 1943)
PRESCOTT, Frank W. (University of Chattanooga) - 3 (1932, 1937, 1939)
PUCKEIT, E. P. (Central College) - 1 (June 23, 1941)
QUAIFE, M. M. (Detroit Public Library, Mississippi Valley Historical Review) - 14 (1928, 1929, 1930, 1945, 1946)
QUALEY, Carlton C. - 1 (Aug. 16, 1948)
QUEENER, Verton (Maryville College) - 2 (1943)
QUENZEL, Carrol H. (Mary Washington College) - 1 (Jan. 25, 1946)
QUINT, Howard H. (University of South Carolina) - 2 (1947, 1948)
RACHAL, William M. E. (Virginia State Library, World War II History Division) - 2 (1950)
RAGNATZ, Lowell Joseph (American Historical Association) - 1 (Mar. 28, 1931)
RAGNATZ), Mary Parker - 1 (Sept. 7, 1937)
RAINES, Mary Elizabeth - 1 (Dec. 5, 1941)
RAINEY, Homer P. (University of Texas) - 1 (Mar. 8, 1941)
RAMSDELL, Charles W. (University of Texas, Southern Historical Association) - 15 + fragment (1924, 1925, 1935, 1936, 1938, 1939)
RAND, Clayton (The Dixie Guide) - 1 (June 2, 1944)
RANDALL, James G. (University of Illinois) - 11 (1937-39, 1943) (including 1 each from Fred A. Shannon, Francis P. Weisenberger, and Howard K. Beale)
RANKIN, Robert S. (Duke University) - 1 (Oct. 26, 1945)
RANSOM, Ellene - 3 (1941)
RANSOM, Harry (University of Texas) - 1 (Mar. 23, 1964)
RATCLIFFE, Emory (Fresno State College) - 1 (Feb. 27, 1941)
RAWLEY, James A. (University of Nebraska) - 1 (Sept. 23, 1966)
RAY, Gordon N. (Guggenheim Foundation) - 1 (n.d.)
READ, Conyers (American Historical Association) - 5 (1933, 1935, 1936)
REID, Robert D. - 1 (Mar. 23, 1948)
RENFRO, Thomas G. - 1 (Aug. 20, 1960)
REPAREZ, G. de - 1 (May 3, 1945)
RESERVE Life Insurance Co. (G. Anderson) - 1 (Mar. 24, 1965)
RESTREPO, Camilo - 2 (1942)
REYNOLDS, George M. (Julius Rosenwald Fund) - 1 (Mar. 11, 1940)
REYNOLDS, Hughes - 1 (Feb. 9, 1945)
REYNOLDS, T. H. (Oklahoma A & M School) - 2 (1936, 1937)
RHOA, Linda - 1 (Oct. 7, 1936)
RICE, Otis K. - 1 (Jan. 21, 1946)
RICHARDSON, Ira (Adams State Teachers College) - 1 (July 25, 1939)
RICHARDSON, Rupert N. (Hardin-Simmons University) - 6 (1934, 1936, 1942, 1944)
RICHES, Cromwell A. (Department of State) - 1 (n.d.)
RIDDLE, J. I. (Judson College) - 1 (Apr. 8, 1946)
RIDGE, Martin (Journal of American History) - 2 (1969)
RIEPMA, Siert F. (Works Progress Administration) - 4 (1936, 1937)
RIKER, Thad W. (University of Texas) - 1 (Jan. 15, 1940)
RIPPY, J. Fred (University of Chicago, Duke University) - 61 (1919-32, 1947)
RISCH, Erma - 2 (l947)
RISTER, Carl Coke (University of Oklahoma) - 35 (1936, 1938, 1941, 1944-46, 1949-51)
ROBB, Felix C. (Peabody College) - 1 (Dec. 17, 1948)
ROBBINS, Roy M. (Butler University) - 2 (1953)
ROBERT, Joseph C. (Duke University) - 5 (1938, 1939, 1944)
ROBERTSON, Jarnes A. (Hispanic American Historical Review, Florida State Historical Society) - 12 (1923, 1926, 1927, 1931, 1933)
ROBINSON, Edgar E. (Institute of American History) - 1 (Jan. 21, 1947)
ROBINSON, J. Lunsford - 2 (1938)
ROBINSON, Jim (North Carolina Department of Agriculture) - 2 (1947)
ROBINSON, W. Stitt (University of Kansas) - 2 (1969)
ROBINSON, William M., Jr. - 5 (1945, 1946, 1948, 1949, 1950) (including 1 to Donald Davidson)
ROBISON, Daniel M. (Vanderbilt University, Tennessee State Library and Archives) - 36 (1931-36, 1938, 1940, 1953, 1962) (including 1 each from F. C. Paschal, Henry J. Willingham, and Richmond Croom Beatty)
RODDIS, Jeanne - 2 (1922)
RODNEY, Imogene - 1 (Aug. 20, 1939)
RODRIGUEZ, Jaime E. - 1 (Aug. 17, 1966)
ROE, William S. (Colorado Springs High School) - 1 (Oct. 21, 1925)
ROEMER, C; E.-l (Aug. 15, 1957)
ROGERS, Edgar F. (Library of Congress) - 1 (June 18, 1942)
ROGERS, Lou (North Carolina Education Association) - 1 (May 2, 1944)
HOLAND, Charles P. (Tulane University) - 1 (rud.)
ROMBERG, Eda A. (Scribner Public Schools) - 1 (Oct. 25, 1939)
ROONEY, William E. (Civil War Round Table) - 2 (1961)
ROSE, Joseph S., Jr. (U.S. Naval Reserve Recruiting Station) - 1 (Mar. 2, 1942)
ROSE, Lisle A. (University of Illinois) - 2 (1952)
ROSS, Earle D. (Iowa State College) - 2 (1936, 1947)
ROSS, Edward Alsworth (Committee on Cultural Relations with Latin America) 1 (Jan. 5, 1931)
ROTHE, Charles (University of Texas Library) - 1 (n.d.)
ROTHROCK, Mary U. (Lawson McGhee Library) - 1 (May 29, 1933)
ROUSE, Tom (University of Texas) - 1 (May 2, 1939)
ROWLAND, Mrs. Dunbar (Rowland Historical and Research Library) - 6 (1945-47, n.d.)
RUSSELL, J. C. (University of Mew Mexico) - 9 (1927, 1929, 1930, 1932, 1947)
RUSSELL, John R. (American Red Cross) - 1 (Jan. 23, 1945)
RUSSELL, Richard B. (U.S. Senate) - 1 (Apr. 12, 1943)
RUTLAND, Robert Allen (State Historical Society of Iowa, University of California) - 10 (1953, 1954, 1956, 1957, 1960, 1961, 1963)
SALLIS, Jerry Price (Mississippi Valley Historical Review) - 3 (1960)
SAMMONS, Wheeler (Who's Who in America) - 1 (n.d.)
SANDEKS, Jennings B. (University of Tennessee, Memphis State College) -6 (1938, 1942, 1946)
SARRATT, G. M. (Vanderbilt University) - 4 (1946, 1949) (including 1 from Meredith P. Crawford)
SAUNDERS, Humphrey - 1 (Feb. 25, 1931)
SAVAGE, Louise (University of Virginia Library) - 1 (Nov. 2, 1943)
SAYE, Albert B. (University of Georgia) - 1 (Jan. 3, 1945)
SCHAEDLER, Louis C. - 1 (May 26, 1947)
SCI1ELL, Herbert S. (University of South Dakota) - 5 (1938, 1939, 194, 1948)
SCHEPS, Clarence (Tulane University) - 5 (1953, 1958, 1959, 1963)
SCUERMERHORN, H. B. - 1 (May 26, 1953)
SCHLEGEL, Marvin W. (Longwood College) - 1 (n.d.)
SCHMIDT, Louis Bernard (University of Texas, Iowa State College) - 14 (1938-41, 1943, 1944)
SC1IOLES, France V. (Library of Congress Mexican Archives, University of New Mexico, Carnegie Institution) - 37 (1926-31, 1941, 1946, 1950, 1952, 1953)
SCILULTZ, Harold S. (University of Vermont) - 2 (1946)
SCOTT, Mrs. A. W. (University of Georgia Press) - 1 (n.d.)
SCOTT, Franklin D. (Northwestern University) - 1 (July 20, 1949)
SCOTT, Mrs. John - 2 (1941)
SEARS, Alfred B. (University of Oklahoma) - 5 (1938, 1939, 1946, 1950)
SELLERS, Ava F. (Vanderbilt University) - 1 (Feb. 7, 1956)
SELLERS, James B. (University of Alabama) - 1 (May 5, 1944)
SELLERS, James L. (Mississippi Valley Historical Association, University of Nebraska, Nebraska State Historical Society) - 17 (1939, 194, 1945, 1948, 1951-53)
SELLIN, Thorsten (Annals of American Academy of Political and Social Science) - 1 (Nov. 7, 1932)
SENSABAUGH, Leon F. (Birmingham-Southern College) - 6 (1946, 1947, 1950, 1958)
SETTLEMIER, Westen H. - 1 (Oct. 22, 1921)
SIIAFER, Boyd C. (American Historical Association, American Historical Review) - 27 (1955-59, 1961, 1963) (including 1 each from Patty W. Washington and Carl Wittke, 2 from Douglas Veale)
SHANKS, Henry T. (Birmingham-Southern College) - 11 (1944-46, 1948-51)
SHANNON, Fred. A. (Mississippi Valley Historical Association, Kansas State Agricultural College) - 3 (1928, 1930)
SHANNON, William V. - 1 (Mar. 30, 1948)
SHARP, Walter R. (Social Science Research Council) - 1 (Dec. 15, 1931)
SHAW, A. M. Jr. (Centenary College of Louisiana) - 3 (1943, 1948, 1949)
SHEETS, L. C. (University of Colorado Bookstore) - 1 (Feb. 27, 1936)
SHELBY, Charmion- 2 (1938)
SHEPPARD, William Arthur - 5 (1942) (including 1 from W. H. Stephenson)
SHERRARD, May L. - 1 (Sept. 15, 1952)
SHERRIFF, Florence Jansen - 1 (Nov. 28, 1944)
SHIPLEY, Max L. (Texas State College for Women) - 1 (Mar. 2, 1956)
SHISLER, F. E. - 1 (n.d.)
SHOEMAKER, Louise - 5 (1945-47)
SHORES, Venila Lovina (Florida State College for Women) - 1 (Apr. 24, 1947)
SHORT, James R. - 1 (Feb. 7, 1953)
SHOWS, S. M. (DeSoto Parish Department of Education) - 1 (July 1, 1943)
SHRYOCK, Richard H. (University of Pennsylvania) - 3 (1939, 1941) (including 1 from John Pomfret)
SHUGG, Roger W. (Indiana University, University of Chicago Press) - 9 (1943, 1957, 1958) (including 1 from Blossom Porte)
SIBLEY, Elbridge (Social Science Research Council) - 7 (1946, 1949, 1951 1952, n.d.)
SIEGEL, Stanley (University of Houston) - 1 (Aug. 22, 1968)
SILLS, Ashley H. - 1 (Aug. 1, 1936)
SILVER, James W. (Vanderbilt University, Southwestern College, University of Mississippi) - 90 (1934-49, 1951, 1952, 1954-56, 1958, 1960, 1962) (including 1 each from P.L. Rainwater, Charles H. Simpson, Jr., and R. Bliss Edgar)
SILVESTRO, Clement M. (American Association for State and Local History) - 1 (Sept. 16, 1960)
SIMMONS, C. A. - 1 (Aug. 31, 1921)
SIMMS, Henry II. (Ohio State University) - 3 (1938, 1947)
SIMPSON, Albert F. (Junior College of Augusta, Army Air Forces, Air University) - 36 (1934-38, r;4o-41, 1948, 1951, 1954, 1955, 1968)
SIOUSSAT, St. George L. (University of Pennsylvania, Library of Congress Manuscripts Division) - 10 (1932, 1945-47) (including 1 from William E. Lingelbach)
SISAM, Cora liutton (Daughters of the American Revolution) - 1 (May 29, 1929)
SITTERSON, J. Carlyle (University of North Carolina, Southern Historical Association) - 15 (1946, 1949, 1950)
SKIPPER, O. C. (Louisiana State Normal College, Mississippi State College for Women) - 3 (1944, 1954)
SMITH, Anne W. (Louisiana State University Press) - 2 (1952)
SMITH, C. Henry (University of Colorado Library) - 2 (1936)
SMITH, Charles E. (Louisiana State University) - 7 (1949-52)
SMITH, Culver H. (University of Chattanooga, American Historical Association) - 13 (1934-36, 1948)
SMITH, Cyril E. (West Virginia University) - 2 (1929)
SMITH, Honora D. - 1 (n.d.)
SMITH, J. M. (Louisiana State University) - 1 (June 6, 1934)
SMITH, J. M. (Tennessee State Department of Education) - 1 (Apr. 10, 1938)
SMITH, James H. C. (Carnegie Institution) - 1 (June 21, 1925)
SMITH, Joe Patterson (Illinois College) - 3 (1944, 1945)
SMITH, Marks - 2 (1927, 1928)
SMITH, Ralph A. - 1 (Jan. l8, 1951)
SMITH, Rebecca W. (Texas Christian University) - 1 (Apr. 25, 1936)
SMITH, Sam B. (Tennessee State Library and Archives) - 1 (Jan. 22, 1965)
SMITH, T. Lynn - 1 (July 15, 1949)
SMITH, V. Mitchell, Jr. (University of Wyoming) - 1 (Feb. 9, 1944)
SMITH, Winnie - 1 (Sept. 6, 1934)
SMITHER, Harriet (Texas State Library) - 6 (1931, 1932, 1934, 1936)
SMYLIE, Patricia (Louisiana State University Press) - 1 (Mar. 14, 1952)
SMYTHE, Hugh H. (Atlanta University) - 1 (Aug. 11, 1944)
SNAVELY, Guy E. (Birmingham-Southern College) - 1 (Oct. 4, 1945)
SNELL, John L. (American Historical Association, Tulane University) - 3 (1958, 1963)
SNIPES, James J. (Selective Service) - 1 (Apr. 13, 1942)
SNYDER, Louis L. (City College) - 1 (Oct. 27, 1964)
SOLBERG, Richard W. - 1 (Jan. 1, 1945)
SONNICHSEN, C. L. (University of Texas) - 1 (Oct. 2, 1944)
SOULE, Phelps (University of Pennsylvania Press) - 13 (1936)
SOULE, Percy - 1 (July 30, 1951)
SCUTII, Percy - 1 (July 30, 1951) SOUTHERN Editors Association - 2 (1944)
SPAIN, Rufus B. (Baylor University) - 5 (1962, 1963, 1965)
SPARENBERG, C. II. (University of Texas) - 2 (1932)
SPAULDING, E. Wilder (Department of State) - 3 (1942, 1943, 1945)
SPAULDING, William E. (Houghton Mifflin Company) - 1 (Apr. 26, 1933)
SPEYNIAN, Arleen - 1 (Aug. 4, 1965)
SPRING, Agnes Wright (State Historical Society of Colorado) - 2 (1952)
SPROUL, Robert G. (University of California) - 3 (1918, 1919, 1938)
STAMPP, Kenneth M. (University of California) - 1 (June 26, 1948)
STANSIFER, Charles L. (Southwestern Louisiana Institute, University of Southwestern Louisiana, University of Kansas) - 17 (1958-64)
STAPLES, Thomas S. (Hendrix College) - 1 (Nov. 26, 1940)
STARR, Harris E. (Dictionary of American Biography) - 2 (l941)
STEEN, R. W. (A & M College of Texas) - 3 (1946, 1949)
STENBERG, Richard R. (University of Texas) - 2 (1933, 1943)
STEPHENS, H. Thomas (University of California) - 1 (July 30, 1916)
STEPHENSON, Wendell H. (Louisiana State University, Journal of Southern History, Southern Historical Association, University of Kentucky, Mississippi Valley Historical Review, Tulane University, University of Oregon) - 224 (1931, 1932, 19348) (including several letters to W.H.S. from various persons)
STETSON, Sarah P. - 3 (1947)
STEVENSON, P. M. (Piatt, West & Stevenson) - 2 (1940)
STEVENSON, George J. (Emory and Henry College) - 2 (1962)
STEWART, Edgar I. (Eastern Washington College of Education) - 1 (July 28, 1946)
STEWART, Frank M. (University of Texas, Southwestern Political Science Association) - 3 (1921, 1922)
STEWART, Irwin (Committee on Scientific Aids to Learning) - 2 (1940)
STEWART, Philip B. - 1 (Nov. 23, 1925)
STICKLES, A. M. (Western Kentucky State Teachers College) - 1 (Mar. 24, 1943)
STILWELL, Robert S. - 1 (Mar. 2, 1936)
STIPE, J. G. (Emory University) - 1 (July 20, 1948)
STIPP, John L. (University of Omaha) - 1 (Nov. 5, 1945)
STOCKING, George W. (Vanderbilt University). - 5 (1951, 1957) (including 1 from R. Fels)
STOCKTON, Ernest L. (Cumberland University) - 3 (1939, 1940)
STONE, Margaret H. - 1 (Apr. 14, 1942)
STONE, Robert J. (Tulane University) - 2 (1957, 1959)
STOUT, Kate T. - 1 (Oct. 24, 1942)
STRAIN, Paul K. (The Torch Press) - 1 (July 25, 1955)
STRICKER, W. L. - 1 (Dec. 14, 1940)
STRICKLAND, Rex W. (University of Texas) - 1 (Apr. 19, 1937)